[
  {"id": 1, "problem": "35+28=", "answer": 63, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 2, "problem": "57+19=", "answer": 76, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 3, "problem": "42+21=", "answer": 63, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 4, "problem": "21+34=", "answer": 55, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 5, "problem": "13+46=", "answer": 59, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 6, "problem": "48-27=", "answer": 21, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 7, "problem": "36-19=", "answer": 17, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 8, "problem": "78-23=", "answer": 55, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 9, "problem": "36-24=", "answer": 12, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 10, "problem": "87-12=", "answer": 75, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 11, "problem": "30×60=", "answer": 1800, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 12, "problem": "54×32=", "answer": 1728, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 13, "problem": "34×80=", "answer": 2720, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 14, "problem": "47×23=", "answer": 1081, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 15, "problem": "25×51=", "answer": 1275, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 16, "problem": "48×67=", "answer": 3216, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 17, "problem": "16×78=", "answer": 1248, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 18, "problem": "28×35=", "answer": 980, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 19, "problem": "77×91=", "answer": 7007, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 20, "problem": "82×76=", "answer": 6232, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 21, "problem": "1/3+1/3=", "answer": "2/3", "type": "分数加法"},
  {"id": 22, "problem": "1/4+3/4=", "answer": 1, "type": "分数加法"},
  {"id": 23, "problem": "3/6+1/6=", "answer": "4/6", "type": "分数加法"},
  {"id": 24, "problem": "3/7+3/7=", "answer": "6/7", "type": "分数加法"},
  {"id": 25, "problem": "4/9+0/9=", "answer": "4/9", "type": "分数加法"},
  {"id": 26, "problem": "1-1/3=", "answer": "2/3", "type": "分数减法"},
  {"id": 27, "problem": "5/6-4/6=", "answer": "1/6", "type": "分数减法"},
  {"id": 28, "problem": "7/8-4/8=", "answer": "3/8", "type": "分数减法"},
  {"id": 29, "problem": "5/9-2/9=", "answer": "3/9", "type": "分数减法"},
  {"id": 30, "problem": "7/7-1=", "answer": 0, "type": "分数减法"},
  {"id": 31, "problem": "117×20=", "answer": 2340, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 32, "problem": "254×15=", "answer": 3810, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 33, "problem": "213×32=", "answer": 6816, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 34, "problem": "174×17=", "answer": 2958, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 35, "problem": "138×23=", "answer": 3174, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 36, "problem": "263×36=", "answer": 9468, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 37, "problem": "707×18=", "answer": 12726, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 38, "problem": "824×21=", "answer": 17304, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 39, "problem": "654×69=", "answer": 45126, "type": "乘法运算"},
  {"id": 40, "problem": "582×83=", "answer": 48306, "type": "乘法运算"}
]